in a world full of the ordinary
we are redefining new ways and
possibilities
too old
says who
must it be round-shaped
who says it can be different
must it be a hint says who
free from the old ways
say hello to our new comprehensive
medical coverage plan
that rewards you with 30 percent upfront
discount on insurance charges from the
moment you sign up
from the savings you're free to do the
things you enjoy
a game-changing plan that packs a punch
take charge of your health enjoy up to
40 ncd on the insurance charges for the
following years if no claims are made
this is not just any plan but one that
offers the best value and more options
so that your loved ones are well
protected in one single plan
now you can enjoy the best of both
worlds a comprehensive medical coverage
and savings on insurance charges too we
redefined the possible to make your
everyday better find out more by calling
our customer care line or get in touch
with our professional menu life advisor
today